Ever since I was a young boy
I played the silver ball
From Soho down to Brighton
I must've played them all
But I ain't seen nothin' like
him in any amusement hall
That deaf, dumb, and blind
kid sure plays a mean pinball
He stands like a statue,
becomes part of the machine
Feeling all the bumpers,
always playing clean
He plays by intuition,
the digit counters fall
That deaf, dumb, and blind
kid sure plays a mean pinball
He's a pinball wizard,
there has to be a twist
A pinball wizard's got
such a supple wrist
(How do you think he does it?)
I don't know
(What makes him so good?)
Well, he ain't got
no distractions,
can't hear no buzzes and bells
Don't see lights a-flashin',
he plays by sense of smell
Always has a replay,
never tilts at all
That deaf, dumb, and blind kid
sure plays a mean pinball
He can't beat me now,
I've always been the champ
I know every trick,
no freak's gonna beat my hand
Even on my usual table
he can beat the best
His disciples lead him in
and he just does the rest
He's got crazy flipper fingers,
I've never seen him fall
That deaf, dumb, and blind kid
sure plays a mean pinball
He's a pinball wizard,
there has to be a twist
A pinball wizard's got
such a supple wrist
He's a pinball wizard,
he scores a trillion more
A pinball wizard,
the world's new pinball lord
He's scoring more,
he's scoring more!
I thought I was the
Bally table king,
but I just handed
my pinball crown to him
To him, to him!